One dream, one wish If you want it,
gotta go over the top!
Setting sail and heading for the unknown.
Cutting through the
winds and waves as I go.
Gotta keep it up, never stopping, no.
Cause I'm aiming to get there first, yeah.
It's all or nothing, no time to worry.
Do it later, right now I'm living free.
When your foes look like
they will overwhelm you.
It means your heart's saying
this is what you can't do.
Despite all that to run is not an option.
Once they're closed, I
feel the satisfaction.
You think I'm rude,
here's my appreciation.
When things are getting
tough, just gotta smile.
If you are going on your way.
And you're looking for
a fresh, brand new day.
Then make sure your only
thought you have is.
Yes, I can.
As you're on your way.
Marks maps will be made.
Yes, with every step that you will take.
Just look at all you've been through.
Look ahead at new horizons.
In view shining brightly.
Oh, who knows what's waiting for you.
Dream living, that's the way.
Make like a hurricane.
Now, got to make your mark today.
One dream, one wish.
Your dreams don't run away.
Go for the knockout.
Over the top!
This is bad!
Go back to the mountain without me!
Are you sure, sir?
Things are about to get ugly.
I know that much.
Even for him, this is terrifying.
And it was over in a flash.
I'd hoped it would take long
enough for him to sober up.
Get back here!
He's right here!
Run!
No!
Dammit! My house! My house!
Daddy!
Third gear! Let's go!
Let's go!
I've got to stop Kaido right
now, so I can't hold back!
Gum-Gum Elephant Guys!
Oh, my God.
Something knocked him out of the sky!
Who the hell is that?
Wait, I know him!
It's the guy who took out a rash man!
General Hold 'em!
Kiku!
I remain unharmed.
And you, Master?
I'm fine.
I feared I'd lost you.
That fear is unfounded.
But the others...
Odin Castle! No!
Lord Momonosuke!
Wait, Master Keen.
Wait for what?
Without him, it's all for nothing.
I must ensure his safety,
no matter the cost.
I feel the same.
It's not that.
It's just...
I think there is someone else
you should be worrying about.
Tsuru
Karoo could wake up and continue
his rampage at any moment.
The townspeople are still in grave danger.
A fine point.
Then I shall go to Okobori town.
And I shall leave the young
lord in your capable hands.
Very well!
You made it out.
You survived that somehow. Right, guys?
General Speed!
What happened?
Those are serious injuries.
I thought she left town earlier.
I thought so too, but I just saw
her fall from the commander's body.
Speed, say something, please!
Who the hell are you?
Hey, what happened to you?
Porcelina!
No, General Speed!
Wait a second!
What the heck are you doing
here in the first place?
Where's Tama?
Please tell me you got her back home safe!
Say something! Come on!
On our way back, we were
spotted by Commander Kaido.
I tried my best to fight, but
I couldn't protect her. I...
I failed my master.
Where do you think you're going, Speed?
I'm scared!
I received a very
troubling report about you.
Damn it!
I shouldn't have left her!
I should have protected her!
There you are, Straw Hat!
What the hell are you doing with her?
We should run!
You got a lucky shot back there.
And Kaido's so big he
probably didn't notice you.
It's not too late to get
the hell out of here!
Kaido got to Tama.
You saw what he did.
Kinemon's friends and both of our crews.
We don't know if they're alive
But if I kick his ass
now, it's over, right?
Come fight me Kaido!
I'm right here!
The man who's going to
be King of the Pirates!
Last breath!
So at last, you've come
to the land of Wano!
Time for third gear!
Aaaaaaah!
Aaaaaaah! Yeah!
You just couldn't resist.
As soon as you get here,
you screw everything up.
No!
Now come back!
I just wanted to tell you that
I'll never forget this big
brew because I've never had
such good food in my whole life.
I can't love you!
AAAAAAUGH!
AAAAAAAAH!
I don't know.
I'll set you flying!
FLYING KIDO!
HONKAM!
FRIZLY!
MAGNUS!
No!
Oh, my God.
4th gear! Bounce man!
Time to finish this!
You've screwed up this country enough!
Now that you've messed
with my friends, it's over!
Kong Kong!
Ahhhhhhhhhhh!
Now, Kum-Kum!
Double-tubbering!
What, what, what, what, what?
Tom, Tom!
Tom Morgan, die!
Oh, my God.
This guy's a monster, but who is he?
He can't die!
Thundermar!
I don't know.
That useless idiot!
I can't believe this.
He's still breathing.
Of course he is.
I don't know if this is a show
of will or simply bravado,
but that little bastard's glaring at me.
Glaring?
You've got good eyes, Commander.
He looks knocked out to me.
What was that you said about being king?
You're nothing.